Inventory of the George Haven Putnam papers, circa 1800-1931
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- CORRESPONDENCE:
  - Haven to Mammy., 7-15-1871 (Box 7)
  - Colfax to G. P. Putnam and Sons., 9-28-1871 (Box 7)
  - Colfax to Putnam., 10-1871 (Box 7)
  - R. A. Fish, Treasury Department, to Mess. Putnam and Co., 2-8-1872 (Box 7)
  - Whitelaw Reid to George P. Putnam., 2-13-1872 (Box 7)
  - William Cullen Bryant to George P. Putnam., 7-5-1872 (Box 7)
  - Haven to Mammy., 7-9-1872 (Box 7)
  - William Cullen Bryant to George P. Putnam., 9-6-1872 (Box 7)
  - William Cullen Bryant to George P. Putnam., 10-1-1872 (Box 7)
  - William Cullen Bryant to Geo1 P. Putnam., 10-17-1872 (Box 7)
  - Haven to Minnie., 7-7-1873 (Box 7)
  - William Cullen Bryant to George H. Putnam., 8-30-1873 (Box 7)
  - Bishop to Haven., 10-21-1873 (Box 7)
  - Bishop to Mammy., 11-2-1873 (Box 7)
  - Bishop to Haven., 11-13-1873 (Box 7)
  - Bishop to Mammy., 12-21-1873 (Box 7)
  - Bishop to Sister., 12-2-1873 (Box 7)
  - Haven to Bishop., 4-1-1874 (Box 7)
  - Walter _rsent to Putnam., 6-15-1874 (Box 7)
  - Haven to Mammy., 6-15-1874 (Box 7)
  - Haven to Mammy., 6-9-1876 (Box 7)
  - Haven to Mammy., 6-28-1876 (Box 7)
  - Haven to Mamma., 7-6-1876 (Box 7)
  - Haven to Mother., 7-26-1876 (Box 7)
  - Haven to Mamma., 9-16-1876 (Box 7)
  - Haven to Mammy., 9-25-1876 (Box 7)
  - Charles M. Andrew, Bryn Mawr College. to Putnam., 10-9-1876 (Box 7)
  - Samuel P. Cole to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 11-12-1876 (Box 7)
  - William Cullen Bryant to George P. Putnam., 11-29-1876 (Box 7)
  - From L., 12-26-1876 (Box 7)
  - William Cullen Bryant to George Haven Putnam., 12-26-1877 (Box 7)
  - George William Curtis to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 6-27-1878 (Box 7)
  - Haven to Mamma., 7-16-1878 (Box 7)
  - C. Sch_ to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 12-24-1878 (Box 7)
  - Sam E_d to George P. Putnam's Sons., 1-6-1879 (Box 7)
  - William Evarts to George Haven Putnam., 1-24-1879 (Box 7)
  - Haven Putnam to E B. A. Merrit., 2-3-1879 (Box 7)
  - George William Custis. to George Haven Putnam., 3-31-1879 (Box 7)
  - George William Custis to G. H. Putnam., 6-30-1879 (Box 7)
  - W. O. Holmes to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 8-26-1879 (Box 7)
  - W. R. Mallor to Putnam and Sons., 12-7-1879 (Box 7)
  - Isabella E. Bird., 1-21-1880 (Box 7)
  - Bryce to Unknown., 9-6-1880 (Box 7)
  - Oliver Wendell Holmes to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 9-28-1880 (Box 7)
  - M. B. Anderson to George Haven Putnam., 1-31-1883 (Box 7)
  - From Emile Pouvillon., 3-23-1883 (Box 7)
  - George William Curtis to Mr. Putnam., 4-17-1883 (Box 7)
  - From Emile Pouvillon., 4-23-1883 (Box 7)
  - Henry, Bishop of Edinburgh to Bishop of Ohio., 9-4-1883 (Box 7)
  - P. F., Oxford, to Putnam., 11-7-1883 (Box 7)
  - Wilkie Collins to George Haven Putnam., 11-16-1883 (Box 7)
  - Wilkie Collins to George Haven Putnam., 12-6-1883 (Box 7)
  - Bryce to Putnam., 1-24-1884 (Box 7)
  - Edward T. Bartlett to Geor. Haven Putnam., 11-21-1884 (Box 7)
  - R. to G. P. Putnam Sons., 3-19-1885 (Box 7)
  - George William Curtis to Mr. Putnam., 3-23-1885 (Box 7)
  - Edward T. Bartlett to Mr. Putnam., 3-27-1885 (Box 7)
  - Lt. Colonel George Gordon, for Her R. E. Princess Christian to Putnam's Sons., 4-2-1885 (Box 7)
  - Lew Wallace to G. P. Putnams Sons., 5-9-1885 (Box 7)
  - Henry Bradley to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 6-30-1885 (Box 7)
  - James K. Hoamer, Washington University, to George H. Putnam., 2-15-1886 (Box 7)
  - A. Barnberg to G. P. Putnams Sons., 2-26-1886 (Box 7)
  - T. B. Alonih to George Haven Putnam., 3-3-1886 (Box 7)
  - T. B. Alonih to George Haven Putnam., 3-10-1886 (Box 7)
  - Madam Ragozen to Putnam., 3-12-1886 (Box 7)
  - Brander Matthews to George Haven Putnam., 3-31-1886 (Box 7)
  - Louis Dyer to Mr. Putnam., 4-7-1886 (Box 7)
  - Courtland T. Palmer to Mr. Putnam., 4-30-1886 (Box 7)
  - L. Stephen to Mr. Putnam., 7-1-1886 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Putnams., 7-25-1886 (Box 7)
  - George Bancroft to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 8-19-1886 (Box 7)
  - George Bancroft to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 8-28-1886 (Box 7)
  - John P. Peters to Mr. Putnam., 8-31-1886 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Putnams, 9-5-1886 (Box 7)
  - Richard H. Proctor to Putnam's Sons., 11-25-1886 (Box 7)
  - Richard H. Procter to Putnam's Sons., 12-19-1886 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Putnams., 12-19-1886 (Box 7)
  - Harry Bradley to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 1-11-1887 (Box 7)
  - Oliver Wendell Holmes to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 1-16-1887 (Box 7)
  - James B. Fry to G. H. Putnam., 1-20-1887 (Box 7)
  - Matthew _ol to G. W. Putnam., 4-9-1887 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Putnam., 4-17-1887 (Box 7)
  - From Edward A. Freeman., 6-9-1887 (Box 7)
  - Haven to Mammy., 6-10-1887 (Box 7)
  - From F. MacMillan., 6-22-1887 (Box 7)
  - From Edwin Arnold., 7-4-1887 (Box 7)
  - From George Raw_son to G. H. Putnam., 7-9-1887 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Mr. Putnam., 7-10-1887 (Box 7)
  - From W. R. Marfill., 7-29-1887 (Box 7)
  - Ca Tyffe to G. H. Putnam., 8-11-1887 (Box 7)
  - From Unknown to Bayard., 8-23-1887 (Box 7)
  - A. Wells to Thos. F. Bayard., 8-24-1887 (Box 7)
  - From F. Macmillan., 10-25-1887 (Box 7)
  - (French)., 7-28-1888 (Box 7)
  - M. Storey to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 10-31-1888 (Box 7)
  - From M. Daniel. (French)., 11-19-1888 (Box 7)
  - Charles F. Richardson to Mr. Putnam., 12-13-1888 (Box 7)
  - Charles F. Richardson to Mr. Putnam., 1-17-1889 (Box 7)
  - James to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 2-5-1889 (Box 7)
  - Susan Hale to Mr. Putnam., 2-6-1889 (Box 7)
  - Bigelow to Putnam., 3-18-1889 (Box 7)
  - Edward Freeman to Mr. Putnam., 5-28-1889 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Mr. Putnam., 6-9-1889 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman., 6-15-1889 (Box 7)
  - Arthur L. Smith to Mr. Putnam., 6-16-1889 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Mr. Putnam., 6-23-1889 (Box 7)
  - H. R. to Mr. Putnam., 7-15-1889 (Box 7)
  - From W. Clark Runnell (?)., 8-27-1889 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Mr. Putnam., 10-4-1889 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Mr. Putnam., 11-30-1889 (Box 7)
  - From R. D. Blackmore., 2-12-1890 (Box 7)
  - From R. D. Blackmore., 2-13-1890 (Box 7)
  - From W. Clark Runell., 2-18-1890 (Box 7)
  - W. Steinitz to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 3-6-1890 (Box 7)
  - From R. D. Blackmore., 3-19-1890 (Box 7)
  - Walter Arsant to Putnam., 3-22-1890 (Box 7)
  - Grover Cleveland to George Haven Putnam., 3-29-1890 (Box 7)
  - R. D. Blackmore to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 5-22-1890 (Box 7)
  - R. D. Blackmore to G. H. Putnam., 5-24-1890 (Box 7)
  - John Hay to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 7-7-1890 (Box 7)
  - R. D. Blackmore to Mr. Putnam., 6-27-1890 (Box 7)
  - Evelyn Abbott to Mr. Putnam., 6-20-1890 (Box 7)
  - From Reginald W. Maean., 7-9-1890 (Box 7)
  - From Au_ Gin_., 7-26-1890 (Box 7)
  - Grover Cleveland to George Haven Putnam., 9-24-1890 (Box 7)
  - R. H. Stoddard to Putnam., 10-1-1890 (Box 7)
  - From Nadaillae, 10-27-1890 (Box 7)
  - From R. D. Blackmore., 11-24-1890 (Box 7)
  - Grover Cleveland to George Haven Putnam., 12-20-1890 (Box 7)
  - From Aug. Chanter_., 12-22-1890 (Box 7)
  - R. D. Blackmore to G. H. Putnam., 1891 (Box 7)
  - Grover Cleveland to George Haven Putnam., 2-11-1891 (Box 7)
  - From Unknown., 2-14-1891 (Box 7)
  - Henry Cabot Lodge to Mr. Putnam., 3-12-1891 (Box 7)
  - Walter H. Page to George Haven Putnam., 5-5-1891 (Box 7)
  - Walter to Putnam., 5-13-1891 (Box 7)
  - Robert Lincoln to George Haven Putnam., 5-26-1891 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Putnam., 6-19-1891 (Box 7)
  - Walter H. Page to George Haven Putnam., 8-29-1891 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Putnam., 9-2-1891 (Box 7)
  - G. B. Hill to Mr. Putnam., 10-6-1891 (Box 7)
  - G. H. Darwin to Mr. Putnam., 10-30-1891 (Box 7)
  - W. H. Mallock to Putnam., 11-14-1891 (Box 7)
  - W. Warde. Faer_. to Mr. Putnam., 11-15-1891 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Putnam., 12-12-1891 (Box 7)
  - W. H. Mallock., 12-27-1891 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Putnam., 1-6-1892 (Box 7)
  - Lewis Sergeant to G. Haven Putnam., 2-22-1892 (Box 7)
  - E. Kemble to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 2-23-1892 (Box 7)
  - From Edmund Dra_t., 3-7-1892 (Box 7)
  - Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 3-30-1892 (Box 7)
  - Frank J. Goodman to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 4-21-1892 (Box 7)
  - Parke Godwin to Mr. Putnam., 4-25-1892 (Box 7)
  - John Fiske to Mr. Putnam., 7-27-1892 (Box 7)
  - T. B. Reed to Mr. Putnam., 7-30-1892 (Box 7)
  - William Dean Howells to Mr. Putnam., 8-2-1892 (Box 7)
  - Anna Fuller to G. R. Putnam., 8-26-1892 (Box 7)
  - William D. Hardin to George Haven Putnam., 10-7-1892 (Box 7)
  - Phillip Brooler to G. P. Putnam Sons., 11-15-1892 (Box 7)
  - Ta_er Si_ to Mr. Putnam., 3-19-1893 (Box 7)
  - Johnson M. Mandy to George H. Putnam., 3-29-1893 (Box 7)
  - William Ramvey to Mr. Putnam., 4-10-1893 (Box 7)
  - Anna Fuller to Mr. Putnam., 5-12-1893 (Box 7)
  - From Maude Brooke (for Stefford A. Brooke)., 6-22-1893 (Box 7)
  - H. Butler Clarke to Mr. Putnam., 6-27-1893 (Box 7)
  - E. Marion Hryee to Mr. Putnam., 6-29-1893 (Box 7)
  - From Ted., 8-13-1893 (Box 7)
  - Worthington C. Ford to Putnam., 9-1-1893 (Box 7)
  - G. B Hill. to Mr. Putnam., 9-9-1893 (Box 7)
  - S. Lane Poole to Putnam., 10-4-1893 (Box 7)
  - From Unknown., 10-13-1893 (Box 7)
  - Anna Fuller to Mr. Putnam., 12-18-1893 (Box 7)
  - From John Yenndon, Greek Minister to London., 1893 (Box 7)
  - Anna Fuller to Mr. Putnam., 2/11/1894 (Box 7)
  - Joseph I. C. Clarke to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 2/13/1894 (Box 7)
  - Paul Edwin to Mr. Putnam., 3/15/1894 (Box 7)
  - David S. Melor_ to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 5-26-1894 (Box 7)
  - S. H. Church to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 6/4/1894 (Box 7)
  - S. A. Burke to Mr. Putnam., 6/10/1894 (Box 7)
  - Rhys Davids to Putnam1, 8-2-1894 (Box 7)
  - Charles R. King to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 9/3/1894 (Box 7)
  - From Chas. Dudley Warrens., 9-29-1894 (Box 7)
  - William Ramsay to Putnam., 10-25-1894 (Box 7)
  - J. C. Ropes to G. P. Putnam., 10-27-1894 (Box 7)
  - Brooke to George P. Putnam's Sons., 11-12-1894 (Box 7)
  - P. P. Stearns to G. P. Putnams Sons., 12-9-1894 (Box 7)
  - David Clancey to George Haven Putnam., 12-17-1894 (Box 7)
  - Charles Sech_ Kingsford to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 1-4-1895 (Box 7)
  - F. Park to Putnam., 5-1-1895 (Box 7)
  - John Kendrik Bangs to Mr. Putnam., 4-17-1895 (Box 7)
  - Bryce to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 5-10-1895 (Box 7)
  - From Acton., 5-10-1895 (Box 7)
  - Edmond Gosse to G. H. Putnam., 5-13-1895 (Box 7)
  - J. L. Stracham Davidson to Lewis Sergeant., 6-16-1895 (Box 7)
  - From Herbert Maxwell., 7-11-1895 (Box 7)
  - From Justin McCarthy., 7-12-1895 (Box 7)
  - R. L. S. to Fisher Unwin., 6-5-1895 (Box 7)
  - Hall Caine to Mr. Putnam., 10-1-1895 (Box 7)
  - George Caty Eggleston to Putnam., 10-14-1895 (Box 7)
  - From Hall Caine., 11-8-1895 (Box 7)
  - P. Amsburg to Mr. Putnam., 11-27-1895 (Box 7)
  - F. P. Strearns to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 11-31-1895 (Box 7)
  - From S. _ockett., 12-3-1895 (Box 7)
  - Brander Matthews to Putnam., 1-21-1896 (Box 7)
  - Joshua L. Chamberlain to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 1-24-1896 (Box 7)
  - Kirk Munroe to G. P. Putnam's sons., 2-21-1896 (Box 7)
  - _arsons to Mr. Putnam., 2-23-1896 (Box 7)
  - A. M. P. Randolph to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 3-4-1896 (Box 7)
  - William H. Powell to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 4-7-1896 (Box 7)
  - E. I. Phelps to Mr. Putnam., 4-25-1896 (Box 7)
  - T. R. Lounsbury to Mr. Putnam., 5-5-1896 (Box 7)
  - J. Cowperchwait to George Haven Putnam., 5-11-1896 (Box 7)
  - J. P. Perry to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 6-1-1896 (Box 7)
  - William H. Powell to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 6-29-1896 (Box 7)
  - Arthur Gebsman to G. Haven Putnam., 9-12-1896 (Box 7)
  - Edward A. Freeman to Putnam., 9-30-1896 (Box 7)
  - James L. Cowles to George P. Putnam's Sons., 10-12-1896 (Box 7)
  - From M. M. Fipley., 10-20-1896 (Box 7)
  - Herbert Molcott Bissell to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 11-22-1896 (Box 7)
  - Lindley _easbe_ to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 12-9-1896 (Box 7)
  - D. (?) A. R. Marrill., 3-3-1897 (Box 7)
  - Thurik G. Peterson to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 3-9-1897 (Box 7)
  - Walford D. Freeny., 5-12-1897 (Box 7)
  - Woodrow Wilson to Mr. Putnam., 3-17-1897 (Box 7)
  - W. C. P. Robertson to G. H. Putnam., 5-22-1897 (Box 7)
  - C. Scl_ to Mr. Putnam., 10-9-1897 (Box 7)
  - W. L. Wilson to Mr. Putnam., 10-12-1897 (Box 7)
  - From Sidney Pickering., 10-17-1897 (Box 7)
  - From A. Huntington., 11-30-1897 (Box 7)
  - William Gillette to G. H. Putnam., 12-1-1897 (Box 7)
  - James Headler to G. H. Putnam., 2-26-1897 (Box 7)
  - William M. Krane to Mr. Putnam., 1-4-1898 (Box 7)
  - Charles S. Minot to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 2-10-1898 (Box 7)
  - Agnes Bluke Poor to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 3-4-1898 (Box 7)
  - William Brough to Putnam's Sons., 3-4-1898 (Box 7)
  - R. Ajassir to G. H. Putnam., 4-8-1898 (Box 7)
  - F. L. Hasmer to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 5-20-1898 (Box 7)
  - James Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 6-3-1898 (Box 7)
  - G. L. Werchic to Putnam., 6-23-1898 (Box 7)
  - James Brock Perkins to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 6-24-1898 (Box 7)
  - James Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 7-27-1898 (Box 7)
  - Moyan to G. P Putnam's Sons., 8-30-1898 (Box 7)
  - R. Reber Newton to George Haven Putnam., 9-17-1898 (Box 7)
  - From James H. Robinson., 10-8-1898 (Box 7)
  - From C. Sc_y., 10-13-1898 (Box 7)
  - From Alethda Wiel., 10-25-1898 (Box 7)
  - Elizabeth Luther Cary to Mr. Putnam., 10-25-1898 (Box 7)
  - From Walt Whitman, 10-30-1898 (Box 7)
  - J. W. Haginson to Mr. Putnam., 11-22-1898 (Box 7)
  - George D. Latimer to T. P. Putnam's Sons., 11-23-1898 (Box 7)
  - George P. Morris to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 11-23-1898 (Box 7)
  - From Alice L. James., 12-3-1898 (Box 7)
  - Katharine Lee Sates to Putnam and Co., 1-2-1899 (Box 7)
  - From Jesserand., 3-2-1899 (Box 7)
  - From P. L. Michie., 4-1-1899 (Box 7)
  - From Edmund Di_. (French), 4-8-1899 (Box 7)
  - J. L. Michie to Putnam., 4-13-1899 (Box 7)
  - Bronson Howard to George Haven Putnam., 4-24-1899 (Box 7)
  - Irving Putnam to Haven., 4-26-1899 (Box 7)
  - Eden Phillpotts to Mr. Putnam., 7-4-1899 (Box 7)
  - From Elaine., 7-6-1899 (Box 7)
  - Belle S. Cragin to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 7-17-1899 (Box 7)
  - Thomas G. Devlin to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 8-23-1899 (Box 7)
  - Percy Gardner to Mr. Putnam., 9-28-1899 (Box 7)
  - F. V. Greene to Mr. Putnam., 11-1-1899 (Box 7)
  - William Winter to G. P. Putnams Sons., 11-18-1899 (Box 7)
  - Harrington Putnam to G. P. Putnams Sons., 11-20-1899 (Box 7)
  - Father to Haven., 1-6-1900 (Box 7)
  - C. Sc_ to George Haven Putnam., 3-31-1900 (Box 7)
  - Anna K. Rohefs to Mr. Putnam., 12-7-1900 (Box 7)
  - John Hay to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 12-15-1900 (Box 7)
  - E. L. Godkin to Mr. Putnam., 1-5-1900 (Box 7)
  - ? to Citizen's Union., 4-18-1901 (Box 7)
  - My_ Reed to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 11-5-1901 (Box 7)
  - Seth Low to George Haven Putnam., 11-12-1901. (Box 7)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 9-20-1902 (Box 7)
  - Richard Le Gallienne to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 12-16-1902 (Box 7)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 2-5-1903 (Box 7)
  - G. G. Trevelyan to Mr. Putnam., 5-22-1903 (Box 7)
  - From Coschen., 5-27-1903 (Box 7)
  - Glen Hay to George Haven Putnam., 11-11-1903 (Box 7)
  - William Winter to Mr. Putnam., 12-11-1903 (Box 7)
  - Elihu Root to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 5-2-1904 (Box 7)
  - James Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 7-7-1904 (Box 7)
  - Kenton Kaneke to Mrs. Putnam., 10-17-1904 (Box 7)
  - Unknown to President Roosevelt., 11-14-1904 (Box 7)
  - Baron Nentaro Kaneko to Mr. and Mrs. Putnam., 9-23-1905 (Box 7)
  - Joseph H. Choate to George Haven Putnam., 11-8-1905 (Box 7)
  - From H. G. Wells., 1-2-1906 (Box 7)
  - C. Sc_ to Mr. Putnam., 4-15-1906 (Box 7)
  - Henry C. Potter to George Haven Putnam., 5-9-1907 (Box 7)
  - Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 6-1907 (Box 7)
  - H. G. Wells to Mr. Putnam., 6-18-1907 (Box 7)
  - Maclean to Haven., 7-23-1907 (Box 7)
  - George Havem Putnam to Bowker., 11-13-1907 (Box 7)
  - James Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 2-14-1908 (Box 7)
  - Charles E. Hughes to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 4-28-1908 (Box 7)
  - Charles E. Hughes to George Haven Putnam., 6-27-1908 (Box 7)
  - James Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 11-9-1908 (Box 7)
  - John Bigelow to Putnam., 11-28-1908 (Box 7)
  - Charles F. Richardson to Mr. Putnam., 3-19-1909 (Box 7)
  - Tauchnitz to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 4-27-1909 (Box 7)
  - John Bigelow to Putnam., 11-30-1909 (Box 7)
  - G. M. Trevelyan to Mr. Putnam., 12-16-1909 (Box 7)
  - Robert Lincoln to Major Putnam., 12-23-1909 (Box 7)
  - Woodrow Wilson to George Haven Putnam., 1-24-1910 (Box 7)
  - W. J. _ay_ to George Haven Putnam., 3-23-1910 (Box 7)
  - Nicholas Murray Butler, Columbia University President, to George Haven Putnam., 4-4-1910 (Box 7)
  - A. Hadley to George Haven Putnam., 4-12-1910 (Box 7)
  - Cougres International Jes Editeure to George Haven Putnam., 8-11-1910 (Box 7)
  - Franklin MacNeagh to Mr. Putnam., 10-13-1910 (Box 7)
  - T. M. Osborne to Mr. Putnam., 11-1-1910 (Box 7)
  - Ben B. Lindsey to George Haven Putnam., 11-14-1910 (Box 7)
  - George C. Macmillan to Mr. Putnam., 11-29-1910 (Box 7)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 12-6-1910 (Box 7)
  - Henry Watterson to Major Putnam., 12-17-1910 (Box 7)
  - Anna Fuller to Mr. Putnam., 1-1-1911 (Box 7)
  - _te Reed McCullough to Patron-Saint., 1-24-1911 (Box 7)
  - Nicholas Murray Butler to George Haven Putnam., 4-1-1911 (Box 7)
  - _te Reed McCullough to Patron-Saint., 4-8-1911 (Box 7)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 4-13-1911 (Box 7)
  - Sidney Calvin to Mr. Putnam., 5-4-1911 (Box 7)
  - M. Newson to Huntington., 7-15-1911 (Box 7)
  - From George O. Trevelyan., 8-22-1911 (Box 7)
  - Nicholas Murray Butler to George Haven Putnam., 10-12-1911 (Box 7)
  - S. M. Dlin to George Haven Putnam., 10-26-1911 (Box 7)
  - Thomas Mott Osborne to George Haven Putnam., 11-7-1911 (Box 7)
  - Albert Gleanes to Major Putnam., 11-10-1911 (Box 7)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 12-2-1911 (Box 7)
  - C. R. Lowell to Mr. Putnam., 12-4-1911 (Box 7)
  - Unknown to Miss Winsor., 3-11-1911 (Box 7)
  - From Edwin Markham., 5-9-1912 (Box 7)
  - Charles P. Adams to George H. Putnam., 5-23-1912 (Box 7)
  - T. J. Osborne to George Haven Putnam., 7-5-1912 (Box 7)
  - Woodrow Wilson to George Haven Putnam., 7-25-1912 (Box 7)
  - Franklin MacNeagh to Mr. Putnam., 8-31-1912 (Box 7)
  - R. P. to G. H. P., 8-1-1912 (Box 7)
  - Oswald Garrison Willard to Major G. H. Putnam., 10-8-1912 (Box 7)
  - Robert Lincoln to Major Putnam., 10-9-1912 (Box 7)
  - From H. Bergson., 10-18-1912 (Box 7)
  - Frederick Macmillan to George Haven Putnam., 10-25-1912 (Box 7)
  - Unknown to Col. Theodore Roosevelt., 2-17-1913 (Box 7)
  - Curzon of Kedleston., 3-13-1913 (Box 7)
  - Anna Fuller to Mr. Putnam., 3-24-1913 (Box 7)
  - John S. Kosby to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 4-12-1913 (Box 7)
  - Joseph H. Choate to Mr. Putnam., 4-16-1913 (Box 7)
  - F. S. Dellenbaugh to Putnam., 4-18-1913 (Box 7)
  - R. Key to Mr. Putnam., 5-18-1913 (Box 7)
  - Beatrize M deBurgh to G. H. Putnam., 5-23-1913 (Box 7)
  - Walter H. Page to George Haven Putnam., 6-12-1913 (Box 7)
  - Oliver Lodge to Mr. Putnam., 6-24-1913 (Box 7)
  - Francis Darwin to Putnam., 6-26-1913 (Box 7)
  - F. S. Dellenbaugh to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 9-22-1913 (Box 7)
  - Charles F. Adams to Mr. Putnam., 10-8-1913 (Box 7)
  - F. S. Dellenbaugh to G. H. Putnam., 11-9-1913 (Box 7)
  - Ward to Major George Haven Putnam., 11-22-1913 (Box 7)
  - Cynthia Stockley to Mr. Huntington. (copy), 12-26-1913 (Box 7)
  - _nt Spring Rice to Major Putnam., 1-2-1914 (Box 8)
  - Arthur Travis to Mr. Putnam., 1-10-1914 (Box 8)
  - Lawrence F. Abbott to Mr. George Haven Putnam., 2-2-1914 (Box 8)
  - Francis Darwin to Mr. Putnam., 2-19-1914 (Box 8)
  - Walter H. Page to George Haven Putnam., 4-29-1914 (Box 8)
  - Charles R. Hughes to George Haven Putnam., 7-26-1914 (Box 8)
  - From G. Ferrero., 8-19-1914 (Box 8)
  - Strachey (The Spectator) to Mr. Putnam., 9-2-1914 (Box 8)
  - A. Manrick Low to Dr. George Haven Putnam., 9-21-1914. (Box 8)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 10-17-1914 (Box 8)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 11-7-1914 (Box 8)
  - George L. _lure to George Haven Putnam., 11-19-1914 (Box 8)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 11-25-1914 (Box 8)
  - Elihu Root to George H. Putnam., 12-11-1914 (Box 8)
  - Ethel H. Dell to Mr. Putnam., 12-19-1914 (Box 8)
  - Lindley M. _nison., 1-5-1915 (Box 8)
  - James Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 1-9-1915 (Box 8)
  - Joseph H. Choate to George Haven Putnam., 1-12-1915 (Box 8)
  - Henry L. Stinson to Major George Haven Putnam., 1-27-1915 (Box 8)
  - Toyokichi Iyenaga to Major Putnam., 1-28-1915 (Box 8)
  - James Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 2-9-1915 (Box 8)
  - Andrew D. White to George Haven Putnam., 2-10-1915 (Box 8)
  - Elihu Root to G. H. Putnam., 2-11-1915 (Box 8)
  - James Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 2-27-1915 (Box 8)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 2-1915 (Box 8)
  - Sonnie Ma_s to George Haven Putnam., 3-12-1915 (Box 8)
  - Joseph H. Choate to Major Putnam., 4-30-1915 (Box 8)
  - Spring Rice to Mr. Putnam., 5-5-1915 (Box 8)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 5-5-1915 (Box 8)
  - Champ_an_ to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 5-29-1915 (Box 8)
  - Charles E. Hughes to George Haven Putnam., 6-5-1915 (Box 8)
  - Buckmaster to G. H. Putnam., 7-7-1915 (Box 8)
  - Woodrow Wilson to George H. Putnam., 7-27-1915 (Box 8)
  - James M. Back to George Haven Putnam., 10-15-1915 (Box 8)
  - Anna Fuller to Mr. Putnam., 10-19-1915 (Box 8)
  - Oswald Garrison Villard to George Haven Putnam., 10-25-1915 (Box 8)
  - Oswald Garrison Villard to George Haven Putnam., 10-27-1915 (Box 8)
  - James Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 11-9-1915 (Box 8)
  - Buckmaster to Putnam., 11-12-1915 (Box 8)
  - George Otto Grevelyan to Mr. Putnam., 11-24-1915 (Box 8)
  - Spring Rice to Mr. Putnam., 12-6-1915 (Box 8)
  - Joseph H. Choate to Mr. Putnam., 12-28-1915 (Box 8)
  - Henry L. Stimson to Major Putnam., 1-5-1916 (Box 8)
  - Ward to Major Putnam., 1-5-1916 (Box 8)
  - Florence Spring Rice to Mr. Putnam., 1-7-1916 (Box 8)
  - Oswald Garrison Villard to Major Putnam., 2-16-1916 (Box 8)
  - J. L. Stracham Davidson to Putnam., 2-15-1916 (Box 8)
  - Spring Rice to Mr. Putnam., 3-15-1916 (Box 8)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 3-8-1916 (Box 8)
  - Henry van Dyke to Mr. Putnam., 3-24-1916 (Box 8)
  - Frederic R. Goudert to Major G. H. Putnam., 5-20-1916 (Box 8)
  - Unknown to Editor of the New Republic., 6-13-1916 (Box 8)
  - Francis Younghusband to Mr. Putnam., 6-21-1916 (Box 8)
  - Charles E. Hughes to Mr. Putnam., 7-15-1916 (Box 8)
  - Charles E. Hughes to Mr. George Haven Putnam., 7-18-1916 (Box 8)
  - William T. Manning to George Haven Putnam., 11-4-1916 (Box 8)
  - Joseph H. Choate to Mr. Putnam., 11-21-1916 (Box 8)
  - Wilfred Lauries to Mr. Putnam., 1-8-1917 (Box 8)
  - Buckmaster to Putnam., 2-3-1917 (Box 8)
  - Jusserand to George Haven Putnam., 2-12-1917 (Box 8)
  - William T. Manning to Major Putnam., 2-26-1917 (Box 8)
  - From Gray., 6-12-1917 (Box 8)
  - Charnwood to Mr. Putnam., 7-3-1917 (Box 8)
  - Charnwood to Mr. Putnam., 8-4-1917 (Box 8)
  - Charnwood to Mr. Putnam., 9-6-1917 (Box 8)
  - William B. Mayer to Major Putnam., 10-1-1917 (Box 8)
  - Jacques Lee to G. H. Putnam., 10-22-1917 (Box 8)
  - Coal Spring Rice to Mr. Putnam., 11-10-1917 (Box 8)
  - Charles W. Eliot to Mr. Putnam., 11-19-1917 (Box 8)
  - James Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 12-17-1917 (Box 8)
  - Albert Gleares to Major Putnam., 1-12-1918 (Box 8)
  - A. L. Smith to Putnam., 1-13-1918 (Box 8)
  - Elihu Root to Putnam., 1-31-1918 (Box 8)
  - Francis Darwin to Putnam., 2-14-1918 (Box 8)
  - Buckmaster to Mr. Putnam., 3-9-1918 (Box 8)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 4-20-1918 (Box 8)
  - James Bryce to Mr. Putnam., 5-9-1918 (Box 8)
  - Bryce to Mr. Henderson., 5-29-1918 (Box 8)
  - Eustace Percy to Major Putnam., 6-5-1918 (Box 8)
  - Northcliffe to Major Putnam., 6-10-1918 (Box 8)
  - James Bryce to Major Putnam., 6-12-1918 (Box 8)
  - Northcliffe to Major Putnam., 6-13-1918 (Box 8)
  - Northcliffe to Major Putnam., 6-23-1918 (Box 8)
  - Theodore Roosevelt to Haven., 8-13-1918 (Box 8)
  - William Ives Washburn to Mr. Putnam., 8-23-1918 (Box 8)
  - Bruce Bainsfather to Mr. Putnam., 10-3-1918 (Box 8)